Contact

karkhilekomal96@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/komal-karkhile-29000712a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Dialux

Relux

Amtech

Languages

Marathi (Native or Bilingual)

Hindi (Professional Working)

English, Hindi, Marathi (Full Professional)

Honors-Awards

AVISHKAR zonal level Project and Research competition

AVISHKAR University level Project and Research competition

Prize at PUNE CARNIVALS by MATA for confident talk and Stage daring

Best student award in 7th standard

komal karkhile

Electrical Engineer at Johnson Controls India

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Experienced Electrical Design Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the design industry. Skilled in AutoCAD, Relux, Matlab, Dialux, and Amtech. Strong engineering professional with a BE focused in Electrical engineering from All India Shivaji Memorial Societys College of Engineering, Pune.

Experience

Johnson Controls

Electrical Engineer

March 2020 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Fire and Security Department

Neilsoft

Electrical Design Engineer

September 2018 - February 2020 (1 year 6 months)

Pune Area, India

PLAZMA technologies

Summer Internship

June 2017 - June 2017 (1 month)

BHOSARI

Education

All India Shivaji Memorial Societys College of Engineering, Pune BE, Electrical engineering (2015 - 2018)

Government Polytechnic Pune

Diploma in Electrical Engineering, Electrical engineering (2012 - 2015)

Dr. Vasantdada Patil school

SSC